<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, GeoStripperActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">GeoStripper</string>
	<string name="pickGalleryButton">Pick Default Gallery</string>
	<string name="launchActivity">Select Image</string>
	<string name="continueButton">Continue</string>
	<string name = "introSpivak">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p><b>GeoStripper</b> protects your privacy when sharing photos by hiding the location the photo was taken. It works with email, SMS, and all social networks.</p>
		<p>Just select <b>Geostripper</b> when sharing photos, and we will take over from there.</p>
	    ]]>	    	    
	</string>
	<string name="introText1">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p><b>GeoStripper</b> is a tool that safeguards your geo-location privacy when sharing your photos online.</p>
	    <p>When you decide to share your photo via sms, email, a social network or a photosharing app, please select <b>GeoStripper</b> instead of your usual Gallery app.</p>
	    
	    <p><b>GeoStripper</b> will automagically determine a default gallery application and allow you to change that to a Gallery app of your choice.</p>
	   
	    
	    ]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="introText2">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>Next time you use <b>GeoStripper</b>, it will seamlessly redirect you to the previously specified Gallery app. </p><p>Once you select a photo in that app, Geostripper will remove GPS location
	    info from the photo on the fly without modifying the original file and then return that GPS-free photo back to the application which requested it. 
	    </p>
	    <p>Protect your Geo-privacy : use <b>GeoStripper</b>!</p>
	    
	    ]]>
	</string>
	<string name="gsText">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>Next time you launch <b>GeoStripper</b> from your favorite photo sharing application, it will redirect you to the Gallery app specified below.</p>
	    <p>Once you select the photo you want to share, <b>GeoStripper</b> will remove GPS tags from it on the fly without modifying the original picture</p> 
	    
	    ]]>
	</string>
	    	    	
	    
</resources>